<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn More About the FileFormats Website (About Us, Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, and More) on File Formats</title>
    <link>https://fileformats.org/institutional/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learn More About the FileFormats Website (About Us, Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, and More) on File Formats</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://fileformats.org/institutional/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/institutional/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/institutional/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Welcome to FileFormats, your go-to resource for unraveling the mysteries of file extensions, file formats, and file types. At FileFormats, we are passionate about demystifying the world of digital files, empowering you with the knowledge you need to navigate the digital landscape confidently.
Our Mission Our mission is simple: to provide you with clear and comprehensive explanations of file extensions, file formats, and file types. We understand that in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to have a solid grasp of these concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affiliate Disclosure for FileFormats.org</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/institutional/affiliate-disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/institutional/affiliate-disclosure/</guid>
      <description>Affiliate Disclosure Last Updated: October 14, 2023
1. Introduction FileFormats.org (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;) is committed to transparency and integrity in all aspects of our website. As part of this commitment, we want to disclose that we participate in various affiliate marketing programs.
2. Affiliate Programs 2.1 Amazon Affiliates We are participants in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn advertising fees by linking to Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Policy for FileFormats.org</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/institutional/cookie-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/institutional/cookie-policy/</guid>
      <description>Cookie Policy Last Updated: October 14, 2023
1. Introduction This Cookie Policy explains how FileFormats.org (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;) uses cookies and similar technologies on our website. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device when you visit a website. By using our website, you consent to the use of cookies as described in this policy.
2. Types of Cookies 2.1 Third-Party Cookies We currently do not use any first-party cookies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy for FileFormats.org</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/institutional/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/institutional/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Last Updated: October 14, 2023
1. Introduction Welcome to FileFormats (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;). We value your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your data when you visit our website or use our services.
By accessing or using the FileFormats website, you consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use for FileFormats</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/institutional/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/institutional/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use Last Updated: October 11, 2023
1. Acceptance of Terms Welcome to FileFormats.org (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;). By accessing or using our website, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms of Use. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use our website.
2. Use of the Website 2.1 Permitted Use You may use our website for personal and non-commercial purposes in accordance with these Terms of Use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
