<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tags on File Formats</title>
    <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tags on File Formats</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:57:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fileformats.org/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>List of All Binary File Extensions (Formats, Types, and Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/binary-file-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/binary-file-format/</guid>
      <description>A computer file that is not textual is sometimes referred to as a “binary file.” Some binary file formats, like early Microsoft Word documents, actually save both the document&amp;rsquo;s text and its formatting information as binary data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “A” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/a/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “A”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “C” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/c/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “C”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All Text File Extensions (Formats, Types, and Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/text-file-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/text-file-format/</guid>
      <description>One form of file that may be stored on a computer is known as a text file, and it is structured as a collection of lines of text. Within the file system of a computer, there is a text file that is used to store data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “P” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/p/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “P”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “D” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/d/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “D”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “E” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/e/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “E”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “I” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/i/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “I”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “O” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/o/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “O”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “B” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/b/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “B”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “F” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 16:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/f/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “F”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “N” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/n/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/n/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “N”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “W” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 14:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/w/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “W”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All ZIP File Extensions (Formats, Types, and Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/zip-file-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 14:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/zip-file-format/</guid>
      <description>Lossless data compression is supported by the archive file format known as ZIP. A ZIP file might include one or more compressed files or directories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “T” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 14:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/t/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “T”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “S” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/s/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “S”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All Common File Extensions (Formats, Types, and Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/common-file-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/common-file-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Complete list with the most common file extensions for all operating systems. Browse the most common file types for Windows, Mac, Android, and Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “U” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 12:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/u/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “U”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “M” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 12:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/m/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “M”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All XML File Extensions (Formats, Types, and Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/xml-file-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 12:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/xml-file-format/</guid>
      <description>(XML) Extensible Markup Language is a markup language and file format for storing, transmitting, and reproducing any kind of data. It specifies rules for encoding documents so that they can be read by computers and people alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “L” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/l/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 11:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/l/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “L”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “R” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/r/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 19:00:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/r/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “R”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All Text and Binary File Extensions (Formats, Types, and Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/text-and-binary-file-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 19:00:56 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/text-and-binary-file-format/</guid>
      <description>The term “binary file” refers to any type of non-text file used in computing. “Binary file” is frequently used to refer to “non-text files.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “G” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/g/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 18:33:18 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/g/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “G”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “H” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/h/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/h/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “H”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With a Number or a Symbol</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/1/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with a number or a symbol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “J” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/j/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/j/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “J”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “K” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/k/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “K”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “Q” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/q/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/q/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “Q”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “V” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/v/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/v/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “V”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “X” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/x/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “X”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “Y” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/y/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “Y”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of All File Extensions Starting With the Letter “Z” (Meanings)</title>
      <link>https://fileformats.org/tags/z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fileformats.org/tags/z/</guid>
      <description>Browse through a complete list of file extensions starting with the letter “Z”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
